jobsense.com 2013-03-25

# JobSense.com | Privacy Policy

We take the protection of your privacy very seriously at Job Sense. Job Sense is designed for you to get the information you need without infringing on your privacy. By using Job Sense, you agree to the terms and conditions listed on this privacy policy. If you cannot comply with these terms, please stop using Job Sense.

#### PERSONAL INFORMATION COLLECTED

Any information that you post on Job Sense can be displayed on Job Sense. We may log your submissions for site improvement and marketing purposes. These records will never include your personal information. However, do not include any information in your submissions that you wish to remain private.

Hearing your feedback is important to us. Any feedback that you send to Job Sense will be recorded so that we can better track the feedback and make improvements quickly and more efficiently.

Job Sense wants each user to have a personalized visit. Because of this, we have created a login system that includes your name and email. Once you register your login name with Job Sense, you will enable a more personalized viewing experience. Logins help Job Sense provide customer service and show the most relevant content to our users.

When you browse Job Sense, Job Sense records your IP address, browser type, searches, timestamp information and the pages you view. This information helps us deliver content that is better suited to our users.

Like most websites, we require the use of cookies. This technology helps us better understand our user needs. Cookies are little pieces of data that are sent from your browser to your hard drive that stores pieces of data, such as your site preferences. This makes your browsing experience, so that you do not have to enter your site preferences each time you visit Job Sense. You may decide to disable your use of cookies on your browser, but that may significantly hinder your use of Job Sense.

#### PROTECTION OF INFORMATION

We have taken strong methods to protect your personal information.

We will never sell, lease, rent or trade your information to third parties. Job Sense shows third party advertisements on our site. We are not affiliated with these companies and clicking on their link redirects you from our page. Once you click on these links, we are longer liable for your privacy. Job Sense encourages our users to read these sites privacy policies as well, so that they will continue to remain safe on the Internet.

Job Sense may transfer non-personally identifiable information to our current our future affiliates. These affiliates include our: parent company, joint ventures, subsidiaries or companies that are under common control. These companies are expected to abide by the privacy policy listed on our site. They will never have access to your personal information, but only non-personally identifiable information.

Job Sense may hire third-party companies to obtain statistical information on our site. This information will never be personally identifiable and will include information like how many people clicked on a third-party advertisement and how often visitors browse Job Sense.

Your personal information will only be shared if it is required to by means of the law including: subpoenas, court orders, warrants or to protect the safety of our users or the public.

#### CALIFORNIA ONLINE PRIVACY PROTECTION ACT

We all need to do our part to combat identity theft. Job Sense complies with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. Your personal information will never be given to a third party without your consent.

#### POLICY CHANGES

Job Sense may make changes to this policy at our discretion. These changes will be posted on this page. If you have any questions, please reach out to us by visiting our Contact Us page.

#### UNSUBSCRIBE

Your communication with Job Sense will always remain optional. You may discontinue communication with Job Sense by visiting our Unsubscribe page at: http:///www.jobsense.com/unsubscribe/
